Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 10, Folder: 15 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Rules and Procedure for the Arbitration of Disputes in the Fur Trade, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Box: 10, Folder: 16 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Apprentice Training Standards, Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Box: 10, Folder: 17 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Proposed Reserves of Crude Oil, Natural Gas Liquids and Natural Gas, Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Natural Gas Serves Our Community, Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
    By Burnett Cross. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Essential Elements in Supervisory Development, Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
    By Robert K. Burns. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 18 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: How to Plan Special Community Programs for First Voters, Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Voter's Calendar, Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: How You Can Help Your Political Party, Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: 1960 Nonpartisan Good Citizenship Program, Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Letter in Reply, Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
    By Brendan Byrne. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: How to Do It Materials, Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Box: 10, Folder: 19 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Employees Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Employees Dental Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Request for Tuition Refund, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Matching Grants for Aid to Education Institutions, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: What is a Credit Union?, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Policy on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    By John Culligan. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 20 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: AHA History, Organization and Services, Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: One Year Under Taft-Hartley, Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
    By Joseph Rosmann. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Nationwide Survey Shows Growth in Union Contracts, Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
    By Henry Juris, et al. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 21 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Dateline Washington, Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Summary of Services, Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Materials for Managers, Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Salary and Benefit Survey, Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Wage Rates, Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Washington Report, Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Executive Compensation and Fringe Benefits, Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Employee Relations, Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Eight Breeding Grounds for Unions, Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Box: 10, Folder: 22 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The New Science of Public Opinion Measurement, Publication (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Box: 10, Folder: 23 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Handbook of Job Evaluation for Factory Jobs, Publication (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Box: 10, Folder: 24 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Development of Interview and Performance Tests for the Selection of Foremen and Supervisors, Publication (Box 10, Folder 24)
    By R. Glaser, P. Schwarz and J. Flanagan. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 20th Year, Publication (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Box: 10, Folder: 25 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Letter to Mr. Peter Smith, Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
    By Andrew Kalmykow. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Statement on H.R. 11007 The Farm Worker's Compensation Act before the Subcomt. On Agricultural Labor, Comt on Education and Labor, House of Representatives, Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Box: 10, Folder: 26 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Men Who Make Steel, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Report of Activities of the Industrial Relations Comt., Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
    By George C. Brown. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Industry's Policies of Labor Relations, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
    By Leo Wolman. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Present Scope of Welfare Work, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
    By T. Darlington and S. McCurdy. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Conditions of Labor Peace, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: The Status of the Labor Supply and Training Activities, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: Re-employment of Ex-Servicemen, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: Half a Million Men, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 9: Dollars Behind Steel, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 10: The Steel Strike Vote, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 11: Steel in the Soviet Union, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 12: More Steel and More Jobs, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 13: Where do Wages come from?, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 14: The Picture Story of Steel, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 15: Employment of Ex-Servicemen, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 16: Steel Ways, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 17: Answers to Questions About Steel in Defense, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 18: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 19: The Best Way to Grow, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
    By Benjamin Fairless. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 21: Weapons that Win, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 22: Employee Representation, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
    By Arthur H. Young. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Safety in Steel, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 24: Wage Trends, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 25: Steel Facts, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 26: The Realities of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
    By J.A. Belford. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Steel Processing Flow Charts, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Box: 10, Folder: 27 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Box: 10, Folder: 28 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Safety in Steel, Publication (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Industry's Policies of Labor Relations, Publication (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: The Changing American Economy, Publication (Box 10, Folder 28)
    By Sumner H. Slichter. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 29 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Practices Relating to Vacations with Pay for Wage-Earning Employees, Publication (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Box: 10, Folder: 30 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Communication Countdown, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Your Stake In Profits, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Inflation, Productivity, Profits and the Steel Worker, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Charting Steel's Progress, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Charting Steel's Progress in 1961, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: Increased Productivity Through Incentives, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
    By R. Conrad Cooper. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Steel's Depreciation Problem, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: Employee Representation, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 9: The First Iron Works Restoration, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 10: Increased Productivity Through Safety and Accident Prevention, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
    By Hjalmar W. Johnson. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Address, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 12: Summary of Remarks, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 13: A Strong Steel Industry for a Strong America, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 14: For the Farmer, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 15: The Picture Story of Steel, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 16: Inflation Robs Us All, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 17: Economic Trends in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 18: Elements of a Steel Company's Community Relations Program, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 19: Publications and Services Offered by American Iron and Steel Institute, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
    By M. Fuller. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Getting Acquainted with Teachers in Your Plant Communities, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 21: A Teacher's Guide, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 22: Partners in Community Enterprise, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 23: Education and Industry Cooperate, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 24: Community Partners, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 25: Teacher for a Day, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 26: List of General Publications of Interest to Teachers, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 27: Steel: Peacemaker for Peacetime, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 28: No Hidden Profits, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 29: Where do Wages come from?, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 30: The Competitive Challenge to Steel, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 31: Activities of the Institute, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
    By George S. Rose. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Steel Warehouses, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 33: Half a Million Men, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 34: The Men Who Make Steel, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Box: 11, Folder: 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Brochure, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: An Exhibition of Europe's Fighting Underground, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Pamphlet, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: New York Post Article, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Incomplete Copy of Letter, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Economic Trends in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Classified Provisions of Fifteen Collective Bargaining Agreements for White Collar Employees, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Classified Provisions of Ten Collective Bargaining Agreements for White Collar Employees, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Steel's War Record, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The Steel Strike Vote, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: The Steel Strike, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Last Man in Line, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: The Conditions of Labor Peace, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Elements of a Steel Company's Community Relations Program, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Box: 11, Folder: 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Labor Scholarships Abroad, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Board of Directors, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Board of Directors, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Box: 11, Folder: 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Labor-Health Venture and the Law, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Your Right to Medical Care, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Box: 11, Folder: 4 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Record of the Tragic Failure of the Most Costly Governmental Experiment in All World History, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Box: 11, Folder: 5 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Freedom to Read, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Box: 11, Folder: 6 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Growing with Schenectady, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Box: 11, Folder: 7 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A History of Schenectady Operations, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: A Short History of ALCO, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Times Union Newspaper Article on ALCO, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    By John Maguire. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 8 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Management Proposal Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Management Manual, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Are you Eligible to become a Jet? - Junior Engineer Training Program, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Your Career with ALCO, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Box: 11, Folder: 9 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Insurance Booklet, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Employees Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Pension Plan for Hourly Rated Employees, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Group Insurance Plan for Salaried Executive, Administration and Professional Employees with Annual Compensation of $10,000 or More, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Group Insurance Plan for Hourly Rated Employees, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Box: 11, Folder: 10 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Evaluators Guide, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Job Evaluation Manual, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Position Description for Supervisory, Administrative or Professional Positions, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Box: 11, Folder: 11 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Engineering, Manufacturing Facilities and Products, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: 1975 Directory of Products, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Merit Review Form, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Box: 11, Folder: 12 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Guide Sheet - Exempt Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: The Story of Corn and its Products, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Box: 11, Folder: 13 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Cooperative Contributors, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By Mark M. Jones. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Course Program, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Synergism, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: AMA Brochure, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: How to Add a Team of 15, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Management Development Course, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Resources for Professional Management, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Audio-Cassette/Workbook Catalog, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Historical Notes from Anniversary Publications, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Special Reports, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Management Development Guide, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Management Development Guide, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Productivity, Wages and the Profit Picture, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By Franklin E. Highton. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Your Career in Management, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By Elizabeth Marting. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: One Million Management Spokesmen, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By Fred Rudge. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Training for and by Management, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By C.R. Rooley and W.M. Leiserson. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Resistance to Grievance Arbitration, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By Richard M. Lyon. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Pricing Management Positions, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By T.E. Wissinger. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Management's Responsibility toward Stabilized Employment, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By Richard Deupree. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Industrial Partnership Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By John Garvey. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Welfare Issues in Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 23: How Big Is Our Job?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By L.R. Boulware. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Lightning and Air Conditioning for the Modern Plant, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By W.C. Brown, A.E. Stanley, Jr., William B. Henderson. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Effects of Environment and Atmospheric Conditions on Workers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By S.N. Stevens, F.C. Houghten, G.F. Begoon. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: The Operating Executive and the Personnel Department, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By Glenn Gardiner. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 14 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Future Meat Supply, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    By R.J. Eggert. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 15 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Little Known Story, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: A Plan to Provide Everyone with Comprehensive, Private, Health Insurance Coverage, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Scope Objectives and Functions of Occupational Health Programs, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Power, Purpose and Politics in Organized Medicine, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
    By David Hyde and Payson Wolff. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Scope Objectives and Functions of Occupational Health Programs, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: What they say about chiropractic, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: The Case Against the King Anderson Bill: AMA Statement Before the Comt. On Ways and Means, House of Reps., Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
    By Edward Annis and Norman Welch. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 16 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Maritime Employer-Employee Relations, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
    By Roger Lapham. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Meeting Report, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Letter to Mr. Lennon, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
    By Ralph Casey. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Public Library of the High Seas, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Box: 11, Folder: 17 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Bulletin; Vol XXII, No. 4-52, Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Box: 11, Folder: 18 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Bulletin; Vol XXIII, No. 2-30, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Box: 11, Folder: 19 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Bulletin; Vol XXIII, No. 31-Vol XXIV, No. 17, Publication (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Box: 11, Folder: 20 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Bulletin; Vol XXII, No. 18-Vol XXV, No. 2, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Box: 11, Folder: 21 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Bulletin; Vol XXV, No. 3-35, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Box: 11, Folder: 22 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Bulletin; Vol XXV, No. 36-Vol XXVI, No. 36, Publication (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Box: 11, Folder: 23 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Bulletin; Vol XXV, No. 33-Vol XXVI, No. 1, Publication (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Box: 11, Folder: 24 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Bulletin; Vol XXVII, No 1-49, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Box: 11, Folder: 25 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Bulletin; Vol XXVII, No 50-Vol XXIX, No. 1, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: By-Laws, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Certificate of Incorporation, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Box: 11, Folder: 26 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Bureau of Information Press Release, Publication (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Bureau of Information Press Release, Publication (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Box: 11, Folder: 27 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Bureau of Information Press Release, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Box: 11, Folder: 28 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Bureau of Information Press Release, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Box: 11, Folder: 29 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Mineral Self Sufficiency, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By Simon D. Strauss. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Declaration of Policy, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Seven Talks About Mines, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By Sam Barker, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Montana in Rotogravure, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Statement Before Subcomt. Of the Senate Comt on the Judiciary, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By Julian D. Conover. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Mechanical Mucking in Inclines, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By Cecil A. Fitch. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Mechanical Mucking at the Silver Summit Shaft of Polaris Mining Co., Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By George M. Grismer. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: World Economic Problems of Copper, Lead and Zinc, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By James Douglas. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: What is Needed in a Sound Code of Labor Law, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By C.R. Kuzell. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Dependence of Arizona on the Mining Industry, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Box: 11, Folder: 30 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The First 75 Years, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Salaried Personnel Appraisal Summary, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Salaried Personnel Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Management Appraisal, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Benefit Program for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: Your Benefit Program, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: Personnel Facts, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: Salaried Employees' Guide, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 9: The American Motors-UAW Progress Sharing Agreement, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 10: Joint Press Conference of UAW and American Motors, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 11: Remarks before the Personnel Institute, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By Edward L. Cushman. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The National Significance of American Motors' Progress-Sharing Labor Contract, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By George Romney. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Committee on Communications, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 14: The Progress Sharing Agreement of American Motors and the UAW, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 15: What American Motors' New Labor Agreement Means to Stockholders, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 16: Customer Sharing and the Nation's Economy, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 17: Employee Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 18: Management Proposal Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 19: Management Appraisal, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 20: Executive Roll Record Change, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 21: Guidelines in Establishing Performance Objectives, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Box: 12, Folder: 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Salaried Personnel Guide, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Box: 12, Folder: 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Music in Industry, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Box: 12, Folder: 3 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Letter to Dr. Peter S. Barth, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    By Andre Maisonpierre. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Challenge of Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    By Paul S. Wise. Item is in English.
- Box: 12, Folder: 4 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Facts About Newspapers, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Memorandum re. Borrowers of the News Photograph Collections, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    By Judith Felstein. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Personnel Program of the LA Times-Mirror, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    By C.E. Clark. Item is in English.